const myCardsTitle = [
  {
    levelNumber: "2.5",
    title: "Cardinal Numbers >100",
  },
];

const myCards = [
  {
    front: "sto (100)",
    back: "one hundred/a hundred (100)",
  },
  {
    front: "sto jeden (101)",
    back: "one hundred and one (101)",
  },
  {
    front: "sto dwadzieścia (120)",
    back: "one hundred and twenty (120)",
  },
  {
    front: "sto czterdzieści pięć (145)",
    back: "one hundred and forty-five (145)",
  },
  {
    front: "dwieście (200)",
    back: "two hundred (200)",
  },
  {
    front: "dwieście sześćdziesiąt (260)",
    back: "two hundred and sixty (260)",
  },
  {
    front: "trzysta (300)",
    back: "three hundred (300)",
  },
  {
    front: "trzysta siedemdziesiąt siedem (377)",
    back: "three hundred and seventy-seven (377)",
  },
  {
    front: "czterysta (400)",
    back: "four hundred (400)",
  },
  {
    front: "czterysta osiemdziesiąt pięć (485)",
    back: "four hundred and eighty-five (485)",
  },
  {
    front: "pięćset (500)",
    back: "five hundred (500)",
  },
  {
    front: "pięćset dziewięćdziesiąt (590)",
    back: "five hundred and ninety (590)",
  },
  {
    front: "sześćset (600)",
    back: "six hundred (600)",
  },
  {
    front: "sześćset dziewięćdziesiąt (690)",
    back: "six hundred and ninety (690)",
  },
  {
    front: "siedemset (700)",
    back: "seven hundred (700)",
  },
  {
    front: "siedemset trzydzieści sześć (736)",
    back: "seven hundred and thirty-six (736)",
  },
  {
    front: "osiemset (800)",
    back: "eight hundred (800)",
  },
  {
    front: "dziewięćset (900)",
    back: "nine hundred (900)",
  },
  {
    front: "dziewięćset siedemdziesiąt cztery (974)",
    back: "nine hundred and seventy-four (974)",
  },
  {
    front: "tysiąc (1000)",
    back: "a thousand/one thousand (1000)",
  },
  {
    front: "tysiąc dwieście (1200)",
    back: "one thousand two hundred (1200)",
  },
  {
    front: "tysiąc dwieście pięćdziesiąt (1250)",
    back: "one thousand two hundred and fifty (1250)",
  },
  {
    front: "dwa tysiące (2000)",
    back: "two thousand (2000)",
  },
  {
    front: "trzy tysiące (3000)",
    back: "three thousand (3000)",
  },
  {
    front: "cztery tysiące czterysta (4400)",
    back: "four thousand four hundred (4400)",
  },
  {
    front: "pięć tysięcy (5000)",
    back: "five thousand (5000)",
  },
  {
    front: "dziesięć tysięcy (10,000)",
    back: "ten thousand (10,000)",
  },
  {
    front: "sto tysięcy (100,000)",
    back: "one hundred thousand (100,000)",
  },
  {
    front: "milion (1,000,000,000)",
    back: "one million/a million (1,000,000,000)",
  },
  {
    front: "miliard (1000 000 000 000)",
    back: "one billion/a billion (1000,000,000,000)",
  },
];

export { myCardsTitle, myCards };
